ILGWU. Independents. Out-of-Business Contracts, 5780/147
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILGWU. Independents. Out-of-Business Contracts
1943-1995.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union
5780/147
5 cubic feet
5 linear feet
Contracts
This collection consists of agreements and contracts between the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union and defunct independent garment manufacturers.
6344614
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff
Date completed:
July 2011
EAD encoding:
Cheryl Beredo, July 2011
Biographical / Historical
The International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union was founded in New York City in 1900 by mostly Socialist immigrant workers who sought to unite the various crafts in the growing women's garment industry. The union soon reflected changes in the sector and rapidly organized thousands of unskilled and semi-skilled women, mostly Jewish and Italian young immigrants. Exemplifying the "new unionism," the ILGWU led two of the most widespread and best-known industrial strikes of the early Twentieth Century: the shirtwaist makers' strike of 1909 in New York City and the cloak makers' strike of 1910 in Chicago. The union also tried to adapt to the fragmented and unstable nature of the industry. It adopted the "protocol of peace," a system of industrial relations that attempted to ensure stability and limit strikes and production disruption by providing for an arbitration system to resolve disputes.
The ILGWU exemplified the European-style social unionism of its founding members. They pursued bread and butter issues but provided educational opportunities, benefits, and social programs to union members as well. In 1919, the ILGWU became the first American union to negotiate an unemployment compensation fund that was contributed to by its employers. The ILGWU also pioneered in the establishment of an extremely progressive health care program for its members which included not only regional Union Health Centers but also a resort for union workers, known as Unity House. The Union also had an imaginative and pioneering Education Department which not only trained workers in traditional union techniques, but provided courses in citizenship and the English language.
David Dubinsky, an immigrant from Belarus who came to the US in 1911, provided strong leadership that led to unprecedented growth in the union during his presidency from 1932 to 1966. He led the union through successful internal anti-communist struggles, built on the ascendancy of industrial unionism by encouraging the formation of the Committee for Industrial Organization, and helped the union become an important political force in New York City and state politics, and in the national Democratic Party and Liberal Party as well.
In the period following the Second World War, the union suffered a decline in membership as manufacturers avoided unionization and took advantage of less expensive labor by moving shops from the urban centers in the northeast to the south, and later abroad. The ethnic and racial character of the ILGWU also changed as European immigrants were supplanted by Asians, Latin Americans, African- Americans, and immigrants from the Caribbean.
In July 1995 the ILGWU merged with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU) at a joint convention, forming UNITE (Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees). At the time the new union had a membership of about 250,000 in the United States, Canada, and Puerto Rico.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of agreements and contracts between the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union and defunct independent garment manufacturers.
Conditions Governing Access
The ILGWU Records, except for publications and materials produced for publication, are restricted. Materials created prior to twenty years from the current date are open to researchers only with prior written permission from the Director of the Kheel Center; materials created during the past twenty-years are closed; the minutes of the General Executive Board are closed. For more information contact the Kheel Center.
Related Materials
5780. ILGWU records
5780/075. ILGWU. Collective Bargaining Agreements
5780/075 mf. ILGWU. Collective Bargaining Agreements. Microfilm
5780/085. ILGWU. National War Labor Board case files
5780/145. ILGWU. Association Agreements. Out-of-Business Contracts
5780/146. ILGWU. Master Agreements. Out-of-Business Contracts
5780/158. ILGWU. Out-of-Business Contracts
5780/191. ILGWU. Association Contracts
5780/202. ILGWU. Operations Department. Collective Bargaining Agreements
General
"Permanent deposit."
Arrangement
This collection is in order by company, as it was received.
Clothing workers -- United States; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- United States; Clothing industry -- United States; A and L Pleating Company, Inc.; A.H. Schreiber Co., Inc.; Abbeville Manufacturing Co.; Advance Curing Co.; Advance Pleating; Alde, Inc.; Amboy Knits, Inc.; AMCAN-Charter Imports Ltd; Amelia Dress Co., Inc.; Amity Casuals; Amy Brooks, Inc.; Angel Knitwear, Inc.; Angelair Bridal Mfg. Co.; Antmart, Inc.; Apollo Fashions, Inc.; Astor Industries; Astor Knitting Mills; American Telephone and Telegraph Company; Bank Products Co.; Barbizon Corporation; Barbizon of Jessup, Inc.; Barbizon of Utah, Inc.; Barlyn Manufacturing Corp; Bayonne Fashions, Inc.; Beebe Manufacturing Co., Inc.; Berklee Manufacturing Co.; Berkley Uniforms, Inc.; Bertard Manufacturing Corp; Best Maid Apparel Co., Inc.; Be-Tre Fashions, Incorporated; Bobe-Jo Inc.; Bradley Sportswear, Inc.; Brockton School Committee; Broderies De Beauce Inc.; Brookshire Knitting Mills, Inc.; Bryan Mfg. Co.; BT.F. Corp; Calvin Klein, Inc.; Cambridge Lingerie, Inc.; Camden Tanning Corporation; Campbell Manufacturing Company; Carousel Manufacturing Co.; Cassaro Mfg. Co.; Cata Inc.; Centurion International Manufacturing, Inc.; Chapel Hall, Inc.; Charlestown Manufacturing Corporation; CHF Industries Inc.; Chow Sportswear, Inc.; Classic Fashions, Inc.; Cleveland Knitting Mills, Inc.; Coastal Industries; Colebrook/Terry, Inc.; Columbia Tanning Corporation; Conemaugh Valley, Inc.; Confection De Beauce Inc.; Confection Du Lac Inc.; ConnectiCOSH; Cottage Tailor, Inc.; Crewe Garment Company, Inc.; Crystal Brands, Inc.; Crystal Brands, Inc.; Cynthia Sue Inc.; D & R Cutting, Inc.; DCB Apparel Group, Inc.; Deeville Blouse Company, Inc.; Del Sportswear, Inc.; Diamond Cutting, Inc.; Di-Anne Underwear Company, Inc.; Doe Spun, Inc.; Dona Ana Fashion Co., Inc.; Dot Togs, Inc.; DPM Inc.; East Tennessee Undergarment; Edie-Bec Fashions, Inc.; Eighth Street Fashions; El Ponce de Leon Convalescent Center; Embroidery Management Corp; Emple Knitting Mills; ER MAR Manufacturing Company, Inc.; Evan Picone; E-Z Mills Co.; F.S.G., Inc.; Fabrican, Inc.; Fairbury Garment Company Incorporated; Fairfield-Noble Inc.; Fairmount Sportswear, Inc.; Faymore Manufacturing Company; First Down, Inc.; Florian Fashions, Inc.; Formflex Foundations, Inc.; Fountain Hill Mills, Inc.; Gallitzin Apparel Corporation; GBS Corporation; Genesis Knitting, Inc.; Gestion J.L.F. Enr; Goddess Bra Company, Inc.; Gold Standard Baking, Inc.; Goodwill Industries; Grafton Apparel Manufacturing Company; Greensleeves, Inc.; Gym Wear Inc.; H.R.H. Corporation; Harbor Casuals of Pennsylvania, Inc.; Harwood Companies, Inc.; Hazle Garment; Hecht Manufacturing Co.; Herman Geist Apparel Corp; Hesteco Mfg. Co., Inc.; Hillside Sportswear; Hilson, Inc.; Holden Manufacturing Company; I & R; Izod Womens Wear Division; J.B. Sportswear; J.C. & ME Inc.; J.D. Operating Co.; Jacob Fashions, Ltd; Jefferson Dress Company; Jen-Dee Manufacturing; Jerrie Lurie Sewing, Inc.; Jim Thorpe Industries, Inc.; Jo-Ann Apparel, Inc.; Jo-Ann Cutters, Inc.; Joyce Sportswear Co., Inc.; Junior Form Lingerie, Incorporated; Kellwood Company; Kenwin Shops, Inc.; K-Mart Apparel Service of Atlanta Corp; K-Mart Corporation; Kollcraft of Pennsylvania; La Manufacture Linge D'Efants Little Beauty; Lawrence Children's Underwear Co., Inc.; Layettes, Inc.; Layton Dress; Leonard manufacturing; Lilli-Ann; Lindy's Sportswear Co., Inc.; Lingerie Lov'lee Made Inc.; Lino Enterprises; Liz Claiborne Shoes, Inc.; Louisa Manufacturing Corp; Lowell Lingerie Co., Inc.; Luzerne Apparel Co., Inc.; M & R Coat Inc.; Makress, Inc.; Maria Fashions; Marilyn Management Company; Mariners-Astubeco, Inc.; Marshallan Industries, Inc.; Medalist Apparel, Inc.; Midwest Curtain Company, Inc.; Midwest Embroidery; Miss Tonie Dress; Modern Embroidery Co., Inc.; Modern Screenprinting, Inc.; Mountain City manufacturing Company; Munsingwear Inc.; Norminjil Spts. Corp; P. S. Industries, Inc.; P.B. Apparel, Inc.; PA Trading Corp; Pace Setter Swim; Palmerton Sportswear; Pangee Dress Company; Penn State Belt; Pleasant Dress Company, Incorporated; Private Label Incorporated; Produits de Feutre Standard Ltee; Quebec, Inc.; R & M Freight Forwarders, Inc.; Raval Lace Company (Canada) Inc.; Reggio Fashions; Riceco, Inc.; Robby Sue Sportswear Inc.; Rosann Fashions Inc.; Royal Fashions; Salon de Coiffure Ahuntsic Inc.; Sayre Lingerie, Inc.; Sherman Manufacturing Company; Shields Industries Inc.; Ship 'N Shore, Inc.; Sidney Berstein & Son; Simmons Canada, Inc.; Simpson Street Cutting Corporation; Simpson Street Cutting Corporation; Skaff Manufacturing Company, Inc.; Sparrow Cutting; Spartan Undies; Spring City Knitting Co., Inc.; State Pleating Company, Inc.; Sterling Stall Group; Sue-Deb Garment Company; Suit Company, Inc.; Surrey Classics; Swanknit, Inc.; Tamac Mfg. Corp; Tejidos De Coamo; United Belt; US Slide Fastener Corp; USA Garment Company; Vanessa Manufacturing Corporation; Victor Bias Binding Co., Inc.; Virginia Apparel Manufacturing; V'Lora Swimwear, Inc.; Vogue Corset Company Ltd; Weather-Rite, Inc.; Wellhart Mfg. Co., Inc.; West Helena - Helena Sportswear, Inc.; Wondermaid, Inc.; Worcester Knitting Company; Youthcraft Coat
6344614
- A and L Pleating (Boston, Massachusetts), 1980-1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- AT and T Inc. (Boston, Massachusetts), 1991-1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Abbeville MFG Co./Calvin Klein, Inc. (Abbeville, South Carolina), 1992-1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Advance Curing Co. DBA Advance Pleating (Cambridge, Massachusetts), 1989-1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Alde, Inc. (San Francisco, California), 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- AMCAN-Charter Imports Ltee. (Montreal, Quebec), 1984-1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Amboy Knits, Inc. (Perth Amboy, New Jersey), 1971-1991 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Amelia Dress Co, Inc. (Amelia and Appomattox, Virginia), 1985-1991 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Amity Casuals/Embroidery Management Corp. (Belleville, New Jersey), 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Amy Brooks Inc. (South River, New Jersey), 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Angel Knitwear, Inc. (Secaucus, New Jersey), 1988-1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Angelair Bridal MFG Co. (Chicago, Illinois), 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Antmart Inc. (Portage, Pennsylvania), 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Apollo Fashions, Inc. (Jersey City, New Jersey), 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Astor Industries/Astor Knitting Mills (Reading, Pennsylvania), 1964-1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- BTF Corp. (East Rutherford, New Jersey), 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Bank Products Co. (Jersey City, New Jersey), 1989-1992 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Barbizon Corp. (Paterson, New Jersey), 1940-1954 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Barbizon of Jessup, Inc. (Jessup, New Jersey), 1943-1965 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Barbizon of Utah, Inc. (Provo, Utah), 1955-1962 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Barlyn MFG Corp. (Newark, New Jersey), 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Bayonne Fashions, Inc. (Bayonne, New Jersey), 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Beebe MFG Co., Inc. (Beebe, Massachusetts), 1989-1992 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Berklee MFG. Co. (Chicago, Illinois) [Folder 1 of 2], 1958-1993 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Berklee MFG. Co. (Chicago, Illinois) [Folder 2 of 2], 1958-1993 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Berkley Uniforms, Inc. (Chicago, Illinois), 1991-1994 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Bertard MFG. Corp. (Lowell, Massachusetts), 1991-1994 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Best Maid Apparel Co., Inc. (Old Forge, Pennsylvania), 1991-1994 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Be-Tre Fashions, Inc. (Catawissa, Pennsylvania), 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Bobe-Jo Inc. (Fall River, Massachusetts), 1991-1994 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Bradley Sportswear, Inc. (Mayfield Village, Ohio), 1989-1992 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Brockton School Committee (Brockton, Massachusetts), 1979-1989 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Broderies De Beauce Inc. (Montreal, Quebec), 1991-1994 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Confection De Beauce (Montreal, Quebec), 1984-1989 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Brookshire Knitting Mills, Inc. (Dallas, Texas), 1991-1994 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Bryan MFG Co. (New Salem, Pennsylvania), 1989-1993 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Cambridge Lingerie (Cambridge, New York), 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Camden Tanning Corp. (Camden, Maine), 1989 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Cameo Curtains, Div. of CHF Industries Inc. (Memphis, Tennessee), 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Cassaro MFG Co. (Carbondale, Pennsylvania), 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Carousel MFG Corp. (Fall River, Massachusetts), 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Cata, Inc. (Allentown, Pennsylvania), 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Catherine G. Matthews d/b/a Midwest Embroidery (Kansas City, Missouri) [Folder 1 of 2], 1976-1992 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Catherine G. Matthews d/b/a Midwest Embroidery (Kansas City, Missouri) [Folder 2 of 2], 1976-1992 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Centurion Int'l. MFG (Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania), 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Century Mills Division of A.H. Schreiber Co., Inc. (Riverside, New Jersey), 1970-1988 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Chapel Hall Inc. (St. Louis, Missouri), 1988-1991 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Charlestown MFG, Corp. (Charleston, Massachusetts), 1992-1994 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Chow Sportswear, Inc. (Boston, Massachusetts), 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Classic Fashions, Inc. (La Playa Fashions) (Ponce, Puerto Rico), 1987-1993 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Cleveland Knitting Mills (Cleveland, Ohio) [Folder 1 of 2], 1969-1991 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Cleveland Knitting Mills (Cleveland, Ohio) [Folder 2 of 2], 1969-1991 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Coastal Industries (Selma, Alabama), 1978-1992 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Colebrook/Terry Inc. (Leola and York, Pennsylvania), 1972-1993 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Columbia Tanning Corp. (Brockton, Massachusetts), 1988-1991 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Confection Du Lac Inc. (Montreal, Quebec), 1987-1993 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- ConnectiCOSH (Hartford, Connecticut), 1992-1994 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Cottage Tailor, Inc. (Worcester, Massachusetts), 1988-1991 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Crewe Garment Co., Inc. (Crewe, Virginia), 1979-1991 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Crystal Brands, Inc. (Reading, Pennsylvania), 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Cutting Corp. (Luzerne, Pennsylvania), 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Cynthia Sue Inc. (Swoyerville, Pennsylvania), 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- DandR Cutting, Inc. (Roesto, Pennsylvania), 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- DCB Apparel Group, Inc. (El Paso, Texas), 1992-1995 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- DPM Inc. d/b/a Campbell MFG Co. and PB Apparel (Campbell and Polar Bluff, Missouri), 1992-1995 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Deeville Blouse, Inc. (Danielsville, Pennsylvania), 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Del Sportswear (Tobyhana, Pennsylvania), 1988-1991 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Diamond Cutting, Inc. (Pen Argyl, Pennsylvania), 1988-1991 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Di-Anne Underwear Co., Inc. (Lebanon, Pennsylvania), 1987-1990 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Doe Spun (Emigsville, Pennsylvania), 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Doe Spun, Inc. (Rocky Mountain, North Carolina), 1989-1995 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Dona Ana Fashion Co. (Las Cruces, New Mexico), 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Dot Togs, Inc. (Rockland, Massachusetts), 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- E-Z Mills Inc. Spring City Knitting (Cartersville and Wrightsville, Georgia) [Folder 1 of 2], 1969-1992 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- E-Z Mills Inc. Spring City Knitting (Cartersville and Wrightsville, Georgia) [Folder 2 of 2], 1969-1992 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- East Tennessee Undergarment (Elizabethtown, Tennessee), 1978-1991 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Edie-Bec Fashions, Inc. (Roseto, Pennsylvania), 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Eighth Street Fashions (Bangor, Pennsylvania), 1988-1991 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- El Ponce de Leon Convalescent Center (Miami, Florida), 1990-1993 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Emple Knitting Mills (Brewer, Maine), 1988-1991 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Ermar MFG, Inc. (Luzerne, Pennsylvania), 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Evan Picone Div. Crystal Brands (North Bergen, New Jersey) [Folder 1 of 2], 1964-1994 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Evan Picone Div. Crystal Brands (North Bergen, New Jersey) [Folder 2 of 2], 1964-1994 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- FSGG Inc. (Hazleton, Pennsylvania), 1989-1994 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Fabrican Inc. (Fall River, Massachusetts), 1988-1992 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Fairbury Garment Co., Inc. (Fairbury, Illinois), 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Fairfield-Noble Inc. (New York, New York and Brownsville, Kentucky), 1973-1979 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Fairmount Sportswear Inc. (Lyndhurst, New Jersey), 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Faymore MFG Co. (Confluence, Pennsylvania), 1988-1991 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- First Down, Inc. (Scranton, Pennsylvania), 1989-1994 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Florian Fashions, Inc. (Cleveland, Ohio), 1989-1991 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Formflex Foundations, Inc. (Saddlebrook, New Jersey), 1990-1993 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Fountain Hill Mills Inc. (Bethlehem, Pennsylvania), 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- GBS Industries (Blue Ball, Pennsylvania), 1991-1996 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Gallitzin Apparel Corp. (Altoona, Pennsylvania), 1990-1993 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Genesis Knitting, Inc. (Perth Amboy, New Jersey), 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Goddess Bra Co., Inc. (Watertown, Massachusetts), 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Gold Standard Baking Inc. (Morton Grove, Illinois), 1990-1993 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Goodwill Industries (Johnstown, Pennsylvania), 1988-1993 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Grafton Apparel MFG Co. (Grafton, West Virginia), 1988-1994 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Greensleeves Inc. (Passaic, New Jersey), 1990-1993 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- HRH Corp. (Hazleton, Pennsylvania), 1988-1991 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Harwood Companies (Marion, Virginia), 1973-1995 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Harbor Casuals of PA. Inc. (Plains, Pennsylvania), 1976-1993 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Hazle Garment (Hazleton, Pennsylvania), 1988-1991 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Hecht MFG Co. (Milwaukee, Wisconsin), 1988-1991 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Herman Geist Apparel, Inc. (Norwood, Massachusetts), 1988-1991 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Hesteco MFG Co., Inc. (Ephrata and Elizabethtown, Pennsylvania), 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Hillside Sportswear (Shamokin, Pennsylvania), 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Hilson, Inc. (St. Louis, Missouri), 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Holden MFG Co. (Holden, Missouri), 1992-1994 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- IandR Apparel Inc. (El Paso, Texas), 1992-1998 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- JD Operating Co./JC and ME Inc. (Cairnbrook and Holsopple, Pennsylvania), 1990-1993 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- JB Sportswear (Fall River, Massachusetts), 1988-1991 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Jacob Fashions, Ltd. (Winnipeg, Manitoba), 1962-1968 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Jefferson Dress Co. (Manchester, New Hampshire), 1953-1955 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Jen-Dee MFG (Manahoy and Frackville, Pennsylvania), 1987-1990 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Jim Thorpe Industries (Jim Thorpe, Pennsylvania), 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Joyce Sportswear Co., Inc. (Gary, Indiana), 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Jo-Ann Apparel Inc. (Ebensburg, Pennsylvania), 1989-1991 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Jo-Ann Cutters, Inc. (Hoboken, New Jersey), 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Junior Form Lingerie, Inc. (Boswell and Somerset, Pennsylvania), 1990-1993 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Junior House, Inc. (Milwaukee, Wisconsin), 1946-1979 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- KMart Apparel Service of Georgia (Atlanta, Georgia), 1976-1982 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Kmart Apparel Corp. (Los Angeles, California), 1979-1982 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Kellwood Co. (Little Rock, Arkansas), 1971-1979 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Kenwin Shops (Atlanta and Tucker, Georgia), 1976-1994 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Kollcraft of PA (Cornwells Heights, Pennsylvania), 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Lawrence Children's Underwear Co., Inc. (Mt. Joy, Pennsylvania), 1975-1993 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Layton Dress (Archbald, Pennsylvania), 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Leonard MFG (Allentown, Pennsylvania), 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Lilli Ann Corp. (San Francisco, California), 1976-1982 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Lindy's Sportswear Co. (Boston, Massachusetts), 1976-1985 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Lingerie Lov'lee Made Inc. (Montreal, Quebec), 1968-1992 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Lino Enterprises (Jermyn, Pennsylvania), 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Liz Claiborne Shoes Inc. (Dayton, New Jersey), 1992-1994 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Louisa MFG Corp. (Louisa, Virginia) (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Lowell Lingerie Co., Inc. (Lowell, Massachusetts), 1990-1993 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Luzerne Apparel Co. (Luzerne, Pennsylvania), 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- MandR Coat Inc. (Hoboken, New Jersey), 1992-1994 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Makress Inc. (Carlstadt, New Jersey), 1989-1992 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- La Manufacture Linge D'Efants Little Beauty (Montreal, Quebec), 1990-1993 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Maria Fashions (Hazleton, Pennsylvania), 1987-1990 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Marilyn Mgt. Corp. (Bishopville, South Carolina), 1992-1995 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Mariners-Astubeco, Inc. (Edgewater, New Jersey), 1990-1993 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Marshallan Industries, Inc. (Cleveland, Ohio), 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Medalist Industries, Inc. (Piqua, Ohio), 1987-1996 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Midwest Curtain Co. (St. Louis, Missouri), 1989-1992 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Miss Tonie Dress (Hazleton, Pennsylvania), 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Modern Screenprinting, Inc. (Boston, Massachusetts), 1989-1992 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Modern Embroidery Co., Inc. (Boston, Massachusetts) (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Mountain City MFG Co. (Hazleton, Pennsylvania), 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Munsingwear Inc. (Homing, Oklahoma), 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Norminjil Sportswear Corp. (Luzerne, Pennsylvania), 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- PA Trading Corp. (Pottstown, Pennsylvania), 1987-1993 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- PS Industries, Inc. (Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania), 1991-1993 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Pace Setter Swim and Gym Wear, Inc. (Winnipeg, Manitoba), 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Palmerton Sportswear (Palmerton, Pennsylvania), 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Pangee Dress Co. (Vandling, Pennsylvania), 1989-1992 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Penn State Belt and Buckle Co., Inc. (Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania), 1990-1993 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Pleasant Dress Co., Inc. (Lowell, Massachusetts), 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Private Label, Inc. (Frackville, Pennsylvania), 1987-1991 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Les Produits de Feutre Standard Ltee (Montreal, Quebec), 1989-1992 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- RandM Freight Forwarders, Inc. (Fall River, Massachusetts), 1989-1992 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Reggio Fashions (Shenandoah, Pennsylvania), 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Raval Lace Co., Inc. (Montreal, Quebec), 1984-1994 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Riceco, Inc. (Kansas City, Missouri), 1989-1992 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Robby Sue Sportswear Inc. (Slatington, Pennsylvania), 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Rosann Fashions Inc. (Thompson, Ohio), 1989-1991 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Royal Fashions (Swoyerville, Pennsylvania), 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Salon de Coiffure Ahuntsic Inc. (Montreal, Quebec), 1989-1992 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Sayre Lingerie, Inc. (Sayre, Pennsylvania), 1988-1990 (Box 4, Folder 44)